martinmadsen

graduate student of computer science

about

Myrdalstræde 43D, 1, 2 9220 Aalborg Øst Denmark

23 years old +45 26 27 36 60 me@martinbmadsen.dk martinbmadsen.dk

7 martinbjeldbak in / martinbjeldbak

martinbjeldbak

languages

bilingual danish/english IELTS score: 8.0

programming Python (Numpy,

Pandas, Scikit-learn)

Ruby, JavaScript C, C#, Java SQL LATEX, HTML, CSS Git, SVN Haskell (learning) Agile methods OS X, Unix

interests

machine learning TDD, functional programming web development healthcare automotive industry

education

since 2014 M.Sc. in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS) Specializing in Machine Intelligence 2014-2015 Studying abroad University of California, San Diego Accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg University 2011-2014 **B.Sc.** in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS)

> Student Focus in physics and engineering

experience

2008-2011

2012-2014 **Student Software Developer** Falck Healthcare a/s

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

2010-2014

Divambu (shut down)

Ran my own small company developing and hosting web sites for clients.

other activities

2013-2014 Student member of the Study Board Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

EUC Nord - Technical Gymnasium of Hjørring

Elected position. Handling of educations within Computer Science curricula at the university, quality assurance of education, handling of exemptions, etc.

2012-2014 Volunteer mentor Projekt Solskinsunge 2012

We arranged bi-monthly social gatherings for teenagers aged 15-18, most of who were second generation immigrants.

projects

2015 **XQuery Processor** UC San Diego, 7 / martinbjeldbak/xquery-processor Implemented a subset of the XQuery and XPath XML guery languages in Java.

2014 **Diversity Measurement in Genetic Algorithms** AAU, martinbmadsen.dk/bachelor.pdf

Concluded my B.Sc. degree. Currently in the process of getting published.

2014 **OpenTracker** ☐ / martinbjeldbak/openTrackerAPI

> Rails app and corresponding Python plugin for the racing simulator video game Assetto Corsa, allowing anyone to view location and information of racers on

track in real-time.

...and many others! I contribute as much as I can to open source and work on other projects for fun. For more examples, feel free to check out my GitHub profile linked above.